Finding Aid for the David L. Carlton Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Kreyling Lecturre-"Agrarians" (Box 18)
- "New South" Talk for Doyle's Seminar, July 1993 (Box 18)
- Woodrow Wildon Center (Box 18)
- N+O Interview re "Civil War" (Box 18)
- "Pedmont + Vaccomaw Regions" (Box 18)
- Media Fellowship Talk, July 1999 (Box 18)
- Reunion Program (Box 18)
- Talk Radio (Box 18)
- Revolution from Above-Notes (Box 18)
- "The South As An American Problem" (Box 18)
- "The State + the Worker in the South" (Box 18)
- NARS (Box 18)
- "Strategies" Talk-UNC, March 7, 1996 (Box 18)
- USC-Summer Institute for Secondary School Teachers, July 1991 (Box 18)
- "Unions + Politics in the Cotton Mills: A Critique" (Box 18)
- Clippings (Box 18)
- 1992 Election (Box 18)
- "Blank Protest + Gender" [JAH MS] (Box 18)
- Wm E. Coshin on Student Ratings (Box 18)
- Confederate Flag Issue (Box 18)
- Carl Degler, "The Two Culture + the Civil War" (1970) (Box 18)
- Benj. DeMolt, "Seven Days in May" (Box 18)
- 2 by Dew (Box 18)
- Ron Eller on Henry Caudill (Box 18)
- FRB of Chicago-Anrticle on Auto Industry + Religion (Box 18)
- Eric Foner, New Intro to "Free Soil, Free Labor, Free Men" (Box 18)
- Gantt-Helms Race (Box 18)
- S.H.A. - 2002 Meeting (Box 18)
- Textile History Consortium (Box 18)
- Tony Horwitz, "A Death for Dixie" New Yorker, March 18, 1996 (Box 18)
- Hurricane Hugo (Box 18)
- Lupold,".S.C. Progressives."-Tables (Box 18)
- MDC, Inc.-"The State of the South" (Box 18)
- James H. Merrel, "The Indians' New World" WMQ (Box 18)